

Thanawit Kaniwaranon DEVELOPER

CONTACT ME

(+66)97-075-5663 kt.thanawit@gmail.com thanawit-k.github.io/profile

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022 : King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

Master of Science in Digital Business Information System

GPAX: 3.35

2014 – 2018 : Kasetsart University Kamphaeng Saen Campus

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

GPAX: 2.65

SKILLS

Front-end

Vue.js

Bootstrap

jQuery

JavaScript

• Angular (basic)

Back-end

- Node.js
- NestJS
- Java Spring Boot

Databases

- MySQL
- MariaDB
- Oracle

Additional Tools

- Git
- Docker
- Redis

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer proficient in JavaScript and Vue Framework, with experience working in teams and as an independent worker. I am able to learn and adapt to new technologies and am ready to collaborate with your team to develop better software for the future.

WORK EXPERIENCES

COREWISDOM Co., Ltd. 2022 - Present

Programmer Analyst

- Analyzed user requirements, developed understanding of functionality needed in software systems by working closely with clients.
- Designed and developed efficient software solutions using programming languages and software development tools.
- Maintained and upgraded software systems to ensure efficiency and effectiveness for clients.

2018 - 2022

Front-end Developer

- Designed and developed responsive web pages and user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Optimized website performance and load times through code optimization.
- Maintain and update existing web pages and user interfaces to ensure they are compatible across multiple platforms.